article-write.co.uk 2011-03-03

# Privacy Policy » Article Write

## Article-write.co.uk Privacy Policy

#### General:

Article write care about providing you with tools and information to manage and protect your online privacy (data protection). We have developed this privacy policy to inform you about what information this web site collects, who may receive that information, what we may do with the information, and how long we keep it. While we have made every attempt to make this privacy policy as clear as possible, if you have any further questions about it, feel free to contact us.

#### Your Information:

We will not give out any information you submit at our site to any third parties except in compliance with a request under UK law. Under no circumstances will your name, e-mail, phone number or address be sold to, or given to any other parties. We will never willfully sell, lease, or rent any of your or your business’ personally identifiable information to any third party. In the case of spammers we may supply information to organisations that use it to fight and prevent spam.

#### Collected Information:

Users are required to give us contact information (e.g., your name and email address) and possibly demographic information (e.g., your post code). Our site also logs all IP addresses, date and time of access, referrer, hostname, the operating system that you are using, the browswer you are using, your country of origin, your screen resolution and the pages and files you access or attempt to access. Certain information, such as your email address, is collected in order to verify your identity and for use in our records, other information is collected to track spammers and potential hacking of this web site. Information collected at this web site is kept in our records (electronic and/or manual) only as long as is necessary to provide requested services to our clients or required by law. 

#### Google Advertisments:

Google has recently begun changes to the way it displays advertisements on web sites such as ours. A limited number of pages on our website display Google Advertisements, mainly using Google Adsense. Google as a third party vendor uses cookies to serve the advertisements on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Google may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Google is already using similar cookies on You Tube. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

Visiting any site using Google Adsense, YouTube or any other Google owned site with advertising will result in a DART cookie being placed on your computer browser. This cookie will display targeted advertisements, based on your surfing habits through your browser, on each Google or Adsense using site.

Once again to Opt Out or view Google’s Ad And Content Network Privacy Policy use the following link.

[**  
Ad And Content Network Privacy Policy**](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html)
